Hey there.
你好。
Happy to meet you.
很高兴见到你。
You're showing up.
你来了。
That's not easy—and it means you're serious about real change.
这并不容易——这意味着你对真正的改变是认真的。
My name is Alexandra, I'll be your teacher for today's Stoppr
我叫Alexandra，我将是你今天Stoppr课程的老师。
lesson.
课程。
Today, let's talk about something that doesn't get enough credit
今天，让我们谈谈在糖的问题上没有得到足够重视的东西。
when it comes to sugar.
运动。
Sport.
做运动。
Moving.
跑步。
Running.
任何运动都可以。
Any sport really.
或者甚至只是...
Or even just...
活动你的身体。
moving your body.
当你想到糖瘾时，你可能不会想到锻炼。
You might not think of exercise when you think of sugar cravings.
但这很重要。
But it matters.
比你想象的更重要。
More than you'd expect.
因为渴望不仅仅与食物有关。
Because cravings aren't just about food.
它们与你的大脑有关。
They're about your brain.
你的能量。
Your energy.
你的情绪。
Your mood.
当你运动时——走路、跳舞、伸展、举重、跑步——你的身体会做一些事情
When you move—walk, dance, stretch, lift, run—your body does something
令人惊叹的事情。
amazing.
它让你感觉良好。
It makes you feel good.
自然地。
Naturally.
你会获得多巴胺、内啡肽。
You get dopamine, endorphins.
提升你的化学物质。
Chemicals that lift you up.
让你平静下来的化学物质。
That calm you down.
这会平衡糖分通常伪装的东西。
That balance out the stuff sugar usually fakes.
你猜怎么着？
And guess what?
当你的大脑已经感觉良好时，它就不会去寻找
When your brain already feels good, it doesn't go looking for
糖。
sugar.
运动有助于清除迷雾。
Movement helps clear the fog.
摆脱压力。
Shake off stress.
释放紧张。
Release tension.
这会重置你。
It resets you.
当你经常运动时，你的身体会开始要求更好的东西。
And when you move often, your body starts asking for better
能量。
fuel.
你不再渴望同样的垃圾食品。
You don't crave the same junk.
你想要能让你持续前进的食物，而不是让你变慢的食物。
You want food that keeps you going, not food that slows you
放慢脚步的食物。
down.
即使是短暂的散步也能改变你的一天。
Even a short walk can flip a switch in your day.
重点不是燃烧卡路里。
The point isn't to burn calories.
而是打破习惯。
It's to break the pattern.
向你的身体展示一种不同的感觉更好的方式。
To show your body a different way to feel better.
你不必成为运动员。
You don't have to be an athlete.
你只需要动起来。
You just have to move.
每天都可以。
Every day if you can.
这一件事——这个小小的改变——可以改变你整个旅程
This one thing—this small shift—can change your whole journey with
与糖。
sugar.
所以试试看吧。
So try it.
不是为了体重，不是为了目标。
Not for weight, not for goals.
只是为了它让你感觉如何。
Just for how it makes you feel.
下节课见。
See you in the next lesson.
我为你感到骄傲。
I am, Proud of you.
I am, Proud of you.